Guide to the Chiron Review Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- March 1996 Acquisition, 1994-1995, undated; 8.34; (11 boxes) + 1 record album storage
  - Poetry events and music performances
    - "Big Web & The Mixed Tenses", 1995 June 11; 1; 01:01:36 (Box 27, Item barcode 39002099363229)
      Weber, Mark. Poems, harmonica, train whistle
      Chavez, Jo. Kanun
      Sullivan, Eileen. Violin
      Morales, Lou. Percussion
      Dill, Stefan. Guitar
      Laferriere, Theresa. Bird whistle
      Thushari. MC
      Welter, Simon. Engineer
    - "Caution: Contents Under Pressure", 1995; 1; 01:01:19; The program is distorted at times. (Box 27, Item barcode 39002099363211)
      "Music of the Flesh"
      "Remnants of the Great Beyond"
      "Her Hot Pink Satin Pants"
      "The State Shuts Up Its Working Stiffs"
      "Seduction"
      "On the Winds of Night"
      "American Psycho"
      "The Devil Owns This Town"
      "Horns"
      "Darkness is My Desire"
      "In Temptation"
      "Selling Out"
      "On a Postage Stamp"
      "Health Report"
      "Poetry Crash Test Dummy"
      "Conquering a Mountain"
      "Weird Gleeps in the Shopping Malls"
      "Streaks of Silver Lining"
      "That's the Office Cowboy!"
      "I'd Punched Myself in the Nose"
      "Gloomy Sacramento"
      "Portraits of Fat Francis Wiggenbothams"
    - Ellingson. Copy for David Letterman (thanks), undated; 1; 01:02:58 (Box 27, Item barcode 39002099363195)
    - Dukowski, Chuck; Cutler, Paul; and Stinson, Bill. "United Gang Members", undated; 1; 01:00:19 (Box 27, Item barcode 39002099363203)
      "Yo Muthafucka!"
      "Public Sex"
      "I Just Want To"
      "Machine Jam"
      "I Can't Get It"
      "Duke's a Kook"
      "Jazz Jam"
      "I'm a Gang Member"
      "L.L."
      "Rock Me Baby"
    - Goodby Harry. "Food Stamp B-BQ", 1995; 1; 00:27:53 (Box 27, Item barcode 39002099363187)
      "Habit Check"
      "They"
      "Rattled"
      "Island"
      "Bombo's Old House"
      "Head Cold"
      "Goodbye Harry"
      "Armadillo"
      "Big Little"
      "Half the Time"
      "Day Late, Dollar Short"
      "Spit"
      "Oakland"
      "Piss Me Off"
      "I Need to Know"
    - McKinnon, Patrick. "Cherry Ferris Wheels", 1990; 1; 00:46:03 (Box 27, Item barcode 39002099363179)
    - Zeiser, Linda Joan. Reads poems from "Two to Tango" / Migenes, Julia. "Smile", 1994 November; 1; 01:34:12; The program is distorted at times. (Box 27, Item barcode 39002099363161)
    - Trotsky Icepick. "Hot Pop Hello", undated; 1; 00:48:44 (Box 27, Item barcode 39002099363153)
      A list of contents is included.
      "20 Nights with Godzilla"
      "Father Murry's Glass Eye"
      "Personal Ad"
      "Dark Engine"
      "Rubberband"
      "Lord of the Medflies"
      "David Charles"
      "Natchez"
      "Oh! General"
      "Empty Reel"
      "Because Love"
      "Erase the Sun"
      "Scalpel City"
      "Hot Pop Hello"
    - Valle, Nick and Dockery, Todd. "Men Shouldn't Waste Words", 1995; 1; 00:55:40; A warble can be heard at the end of the program. (Box 27, Item barcode 39002099363146)
    - Various Poets, "United States of Poetry", undated; 1; 00:56:45; An echo can be heard during the program. (Box 27, Item barcode 39002099363138)
      "Henry Real Bird"
      "Opening"
      "Thylias Moss"
      "Leonard Cohen"
      "Found Poetry #1-Soldiers Drill"
      "Pedro Pietri"
      "Emily XYZ w/Barlett"
      "Matt Cook"
      "Ruth Forman"
      "Tracie Morris"
      "Amiri Baraka"
      "Pearl Cleage"
      "Paul Beatty"
      "Indran Amirthanayagam"
      "Allen Ginsberg"
      "Hal Sirowitz"
      "C.D. Wright"
      "Al"
      "Found Poetry #3-Double Dutch Rhymes"
      "Lois-Ann Yamanaka"
      "Lypsinka"
      "Found Poetry #2-Cheerleader Chants"
      "Robert Creeley"
      "Czeslaw Milosz"
      "James Still"
      "Found Poetry #4-Square Dance Caller"
      "Maggie Estep"
      "Lou Reed"
      "Dennis Cooper"
      "Sparrow"
      "Quincy Troupe"
      "Joseph Brodsky"
      "Miguel Algarin"
      "Besmilr Brigham"
      "Sawyer Shefts"
      "John Trudell"
      "Opening Reprise"
    - "Zap" / "X-it", 1994 August 19; 1; 01:34:17; High frequency noise can be heard at about 46 minutes in. (Box 27, Item barcode 39002099363120)
    - Zark, Bob. "The Gates of Boombox Heaven", 1994; 1; 00:25:02 (Box 27, Item barcode 39002099363104)
      "A Half-Assed Age of Indifference"
      "Phantoms"
      "Obnoxious Attorney!"
      "Pelicans"
      "The Greater North American Express"
      "The Wastelands of West Texas"
      "I Roamed Beyond the Barrier"
      "The Rampage"
      "These Things"
      "I Can't Stand Myself"
    - "Shadows of Myself / Poems by M. [Harhavery]", 1979; 1; 00:31:17; High background noise can be heard on the tape. Static and warbling can be heard in the program. The program is distorted at times. (Box 27, Item barcode 39002099363112)
    - Jackson, Lorri. "From Obero", 1995 February 12; 1; 01:36:22; Static can be heard on the tape. The recording is at a low level on the left channel from 32:18-38:58. (Box 27, Item barcode 39002099363245)
    - Belile, Elisabeth. "Your Only Other Option is Surgery", 1 CD (Box 28)
    - Berry, Iris. "Life on the Edge in Stilettos", 1 CD (Box 28)
    - Brewer, Jack. "Rhythm or Suicide", 1 CD (Box 28)
    - Campos, Luis. "Poetry!", 1 CD (Box 28)
    - Freeman, Lisa. "Rough Roads", 1 CD (Box 28)
    - Gynomite. "Fearless Feminist Porn", 1 CD (Box 29)
    - Hankin, Larry. "Pomes & Stories", 1 CD (Box 29)
    - Lally, Michael. "What You Find There", 1 CD (Box 29)
    - Manning, Lynne. "Clarity of Vision", 1 CD (Box 29)
    - Pantino, Deborah. "Nocturnal", 1 CD (Box 29)
    - Pantino, Deborah. "Nocturnal", 1 CD (Box 30)
    - Sims, Willie. "Story Yeller", 1 CD (Box 30)
    - Quincy Troupe. "Root Doctor", 1 CD (Box 30)
    - Red Dog. "Dingle", 1 CD (Box 30)
    - Ritter, Julie. "Medicine Show", 1 CD (Box 30)
    - Trotsky Icepick. "Carpetbomb the Riff", 1 CD (Box 31)
    - Young, Noah, Dr. "Freaks: No Fear of Contagion", 1 CD (Box 31)
    - "Internal Journal, Vol. 11", 1 CD (Box 31)
    - Vranich, Mick. "Idols of Fear", 1 CD (Box 31)
    - Rig. "Belly to the Ground", 1 33 1/3 vinyl sound disk (Box 32 (Record album storage))
  - Other Papers
    - Manuscripts removed from books, 6 (Box 25)
    - Chiron Review poster (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - Unidentified, 7 (Box 25)
- October 1999 Acquisition, 1979-1999, undated; 13.66; (20 boxes) + 1 record album storage
  Boxes 48-50 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Correspondence
    - Unsorted, 1996-1999; 30 (Box 33)
    - Unsorted, 1996-1999; 30 (Box 34)
    - Unsorted, 1996-1999; 23; Includes 6 3.5 inch computer disks (Box 35)
    - Unsorted, 1997-1999; 6 3.5 inch computer disks
      - Chiron Review archives Michael Hathaway Letters - 1997, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0083; 1 (Box 52)
        Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - Chiron Review archives Michael Hathaway Letters June 1- Sept. 18, 1999 (Disk 2), 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0084; 1 (Box 52)
      - Chiron Review archives Michael Hathaway Letters Jan. 1 - May 31, 1999 (Disk 1), 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0085; 1 (Box 52)
      - Chiron Review archives Michael Hathaway Personal Letters - 1998, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0086; 1 (Box 52)
      - Chiron Review archives Michael Hathaway CR letters - 1998 Disk 2, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0087; 1 (Box 52)
      - Chiron Review archives Michael Hathaway CR letters - 1998 Disk 1, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0088; 1 (Box 52)
  - Chiron Review Issues
    - Chiron Review 45 (1995 winter) (mechanicals) (Box 43 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 46 and 47 (1996 spring/summer), 6 (Box 35)
    - Chiron Review 46-47 (1996 spring/summer) (mechanicals) (Box 43 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 48 (1996 autumn), 5 (Box 36)
    - Chiron Review 48 (1996 autumn) (mechanicals) (Box 43 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 49 (1996 winter), 5 (Box 36)
    - Chiron Review 49 (1996 winter) (mechanicals) (Box 43 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 50 (1997 spring), 5 (Box 36)
    - Chiron Review 50 (1997 spring) (mechanicals) (Box 44 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 51 (1997 summer), 5 (Box 36)
    - Chiron Review 51 (1997 summer) (mechanicals) (Box 44 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 52 (1997 winter), 5 (Box 37)
    - Chiron Review 52 (1997 winter) (mechanicals) (Box 44 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 53 (1998 spring), 5 (Box 37)
    - Chiron Review 53 (1998 spring) (mechanicals) (Box 44 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 54 (1998 summer), 5 (Box 37)
    - Chiron Review 54 (1999 summer) (mechanicals) (Box 44 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 55 (1998 autumn), 5 (Box 37)
    - Chiron Review 55 (1998 autumn) (mechanicals) (Box 45 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 56 (1998 winter), 5 (Box 38)
    - Chiron Review 56 (1998 winter) (mechanicals) (Box 45 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 57 (1999 spring), 5 (Box 38)
    - Chiron Review 57 (1999 spring) (mechanicals) (Box 45 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 58 (1999 summer), 5 (Box 38)
    - Chiron Review 58 (1999 summer) (mechanicals) (Box 45 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 59 (1999 autumn), 4 (Box 38)
    - Chiron Review. Unidentified (reviews submitted to Chiron Review ), 23 3.5 inch computer disks
      - Impetus.doc Review of "The Best of Impetus" by Tim W. Brown MS-Word, ver. 7.0, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0002; 1 (Box 52)
      - R. Peters rev. of P Trachtenberg Alphabet Song Windows Word Perfect, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0003; 1 (Box 52)
      - R Peters celebs.neh RVWS.BRO [illegible] no H.C., 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0007; 1 (Box 52)
      - B:\CHIRON.REV review Poor People, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0015; 1 (Box 52)
      - TALKING ABOUT MICHAEL McNEILLEY BY OBERC, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0016; 1 (Box 52)
      - Reviews on IBM/Microsoft Word Mike Horancsek 1889 Algonquin Kent, OH 44240 330-677-0333, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0020; 1 (Box 52)
      - RP Review of Lerner + DILLARD WPC.1 Windows 95, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0021; 1 (Box 52)
      - Reviews by Michael McIrvin of Wm Doreski's Piano in the Woods + Maggie Jaffe's How the West was one, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0022; 1 (Box 52)
      - Louis McKee's Review of Lynne Savitt's book, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0023; 1 (Box 52)
      - Snydal on Brodsky, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0026; 1 (Box 52)
      - Rochelle Holt Anaïs Nin Robert Zaller WordPerfect 5.0, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0027; 1 (Box 52)
      - Chorlton on Zapata + 3 poems review done, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0035; 1 (Box 52)
      - R. Peters on M.C. Ford 11/17/98 HC, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0040; 1 (Box 52)
      - TALKING ABOUT LORRI JACKSON BY OBERC, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0041; 1 (Box 52)
      - Will Inman Review by Pauline Mounsey Microsoft Works chiron.wps - file type: Works WP chiron2.wps - file type Word for Windows 2, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0042; 1 (Box 52)
      - Review of Ghost Radio by Tim W. Brown, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0048; 1 (Box 52)
      - Rev. of Maggie Jaffe's 7th Circle by Michael McIrvin, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0052; 1 (Box 52)
      - Linda Lerner Review of Daniel Crocker's Book - People Everyday - Word 6.0 for Mac, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0055; 1 (Box 52)
      - Word for Mac (6.0.1) Review of Amy Clansen's 40th Century Man Linda Lerner could not open, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0060; 1 (Box 52)
      - Word 6.0 for Mac. Review of Julia Vanograd's Poems Linda Lerner can't open HC, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0064; 1 (Box 52)
      - rev: Clemency by Colette Inez by Tyrone Williams, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0066; 1 (Box 52)
      - Review of "A Ritual of Drowning" by Lesléa Neuman (MicroSoft Word 5.0) HC, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0068; 1 (Box 52)
      - R. Peters 3 Reviews No HC on 2, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0080; 1 (Box 52)
    - Chiron Review. Unidentified (writings submitted to Chiron Review ), 50 3.5 inch computer disks
      - Microsoft Word INVITE.DOC Tom Hansen's "Invitation", 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0001; 1 (Box 52)
      - R Peters WP 95 gayanth.wpd Hofst.WPD Potts.WPD 6 pg no HC, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0004; 1 (Box 52)
      - "Adventures of a Minor Poet" -- Starkey WP6.1 + ASCII, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0005; 1 (Box 52)
      - Buddha's Embrace Word Perfect 5.0 Gary Every PO. Box 5419 Oracle AZ 85623 (520) 896-9521, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0009; 1 (Box 52)
      - Cara Chamberlain PO Box 342 Fort Kent, ME 04743 short story "The Object" and bio, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0010; 1 (Box 52)
      - JESSICA TREAT PIE Fixed file is under heremike.Dot, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0011; 1 (Box 52)
      - "TallBoys" (story) by Peter Donahue "T-boys" (Filename), 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0012; 1 (Box 52)
      - "I Recommend" by Carrie Laning, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0013; 1 (Box 52)
      - Olds Wperfect 8, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0014; 1 (Box 52)
      - Winans Bukowski 2nd Coming, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0019; 1 (Box 52)
      - CHIRON REVIEW Lechliter Beyond Dis. Waring Up., 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0024; 1 (Box 52)
      - Chiron: cervix song memory for a past love brief bio [microsoft word, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0028; 1 (Box 52)
      - To: CHIRON REVIEW FROM: PAYNE, JOHN D, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0030; 1 (Box 52)
      - Douglas Airmet Bards material Chiron 12/18/98 HC, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0031; 1 (Box 52)
      - Dave Church Poems + Biography, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0032; 1 (Box 52)
      - Real Art (Microsoft Word 97) John Berbrich 3700 County Route 24 Russell, NY 13684, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0033; 1 (Box 52)
      - 1-22-99 To: CHIRON RVW From: JOHN PAYNE CONTENTS: FICTION: "BLOOD"; Bio. IBM HC, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0034; 1 (Box 52)
      - "Elvis, Axl, and Me" by Janice Eidus (in Word Perfect 5.1.), 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0036; 1 (Box 52)
      - "A Healing Hand" by Robert Ervin Layden 2bz: Ms Works 4.0 3a: Word 97. Please cover letter for more explanation, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0037; 1 (Box 52)
      - a:\dutchman "Bribing a Dutchman" John Brantingham, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0038; 1 (Box 52)
      - ALWAYS Notes + Ack- I HOPE!, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0039; 1 (Box 52)
      - octine CB list - copy 10/21/93, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0043; 1 (Box 52)
      - Lisa C. Tayler The Price Something Greater Pain's Friend c.1998, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0044; 1 (Box 52)
      - WP 6.0 Linda Rochelleau submissions bio - summer '99, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0045; 1 (Box 52)
      - Michael S. Smith The change for Love I'm Not Like You, Dad Mincemeat Pie Word 97, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0046; 1 (Box 52)
      - david hernandez (562) 865-9412 syrup@jps.net davidsPoems.doc PC, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0047; 1 (Box 52)
      - MS-Word 6.0 pod.doc red59.doc poems Michael L. Phillips 760-375-2947, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0049; 1 (Box 52)
      - "Tea with Jesus" by Andrew Geyer, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0050; 1 (Box 52)
      - Jennifer Can "Weather" fic. HC IBM, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0051; 1 (Box 52)
      - MICHAEL'S DISKETTE CHAPBOOK CARL MILLER DANIELS, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0053; 1 (Box 52)
      - TRISTRAM: NINE LOCKS (FOR M. HATHAWAY), 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0056; 1 (Box 52)
      - Short Story Blind Drunk For Mac 5.1 (WORD) Gregory Sanders 1123 1/4 N. Detroit St. West Hollywood, CA 90046, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0057; 1 (Box 52)
      - MICROSOFT WORD 6.0.1 for Macintosh Melissa Huseman Poems: "The Pink Mouth" "Blue Cellophane" Bio, also, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0058; 1 (Box 52)
      - John Vanderslice "Running" for Chiron Review 1. Write Now 4.0 2. RTF 3. MS Works, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0059; 1 (Box 52)
      - Alison's Poems for Chiron Review, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0061; 1 (Box 52)
      - GLENN BACH "JAYWALKING" 256 CORONADO AVE#C LONG BEACH CA 90803, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0062; 1 (Box 52)
      - Franz Neuman short story "In With The Masters" IBM HC, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0063; 1 (Box 52)
      - Locklin Candy Bar CHIRON REVIEW Michael Hathaway, Ed. 702 North Prairie Saint John, KS 67576-1516, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0065; 1 (Box 52)
      - C:\WP51\DOC\INSCRIBE.DOC WP51 MATTFIEL.DOC ORGANIC.DOC Patricia Cherin poems, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0067; 1 (Box 52)
      - Jeff Weddle's Poems for Chiron Review, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0069; 1 (Box 52)
      - Rick Lupert 5336 Kester Ave. #103 Sherman Oaks CA 91411 818-995-4457 photo, poems + bio., 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0071; 1 (Box 52)
      - Talkington fiction, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0072; 1 (Box 52)
      - CHRIS DALY "LATE KID" EM Microsoft 5.1, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0073; 1 (Box 52)
      - Maynard Dountown Poets HC, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0074; 1 (Box 52)
      - Dunkelberg translation of Paul Snoek, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0075; 1 (Box 52)
      - Skip Sterling K. Eisiminger 209 Blue Ridge Drive Clemson, SC 29631 3 poems + bio. MacIntosh (McWrite II), 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0076; 1 (Box 52)
      - Al Hudler, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0078; 1 (Box 52)
      - A Book of Poems Ron McFarland No HC, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0079; 1 (Box 52)
      - KEEPING TRACK (gay, final version, 1998) saved as "keepingt.98m" in MS WORD 6.0 "keepingt.98w" in Wperfect 6.1 CHARLES DERRY BIOGRAPHY saved as "biograph.98m" in MS WORD 6.0 "biograph.98w" in Wperfect 6.1 DISCARD PREVIOUS VERSIONS, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0081; 1 (Box 52)
      - A: Butterfl/Geezus Lee at 1310 Odd St. FT WORTH, TX 76106 Home 8176265523 Wk 8172340239, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0082; 1 (Box 52)
    - Chiron Review. Unidentified (" Chiron Review Q/A"), 3 3.5 inch computer disks
      - Disk 2 - blank copy of Q+A disk 2 w/CHIRON, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0006; 1 (Box 52)
      - Q+A Disk 2 Regular sub. list copy 12/12/90 copy 12/15/91, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0029; 1 (Box 52)
      - Q+A Disk 2 File, Report Data File: CHIRON: Regular Sub List new fields - 1/91@1, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0077; 1 (Box 52)
  - Writings by Michael Hathaway
    - Epistle, 1998-99; 9 (Box 39)
  - Other Writings
    - Edwards, Connie. "The Girl That Time Passed By", 1979; 3 (Box 39)
    - Lynn, Catherine. "The White Dress", 1996; 5 (Box 39)
    - McDaniel, Wilma. "Shirtwaist Women", 1996 (Box 39)
    - McFarland, Ron. "The Poet of the Academy", 1 3.5 inch computer disk
      - The Poet + the Academy (titled - David Rivard) Ron McFarland HC, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0089; 1 (Box 52)
    - Sonnenfeld, M. "Works", 1 audiocassette (Box 48)
    - Subraman, Belinda. "Finding Reality in Myth: Travels With Belinda" (Box 39)
    - Seguev, John. "3 Poems", 1 3.5 inch computer disk
      - 3 Poems by John Degun St. Joseph Mo. HC for 2 not for "the way they are", 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0090; 1 (Box 52)
    - "Interviews", 6 3.5 inch computer disks
      - 4/99 Interview w/L.A. Bogen by J. O'Halloran HC IBM, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0008; 1 (Box 52)
      - Interview with Jay Marvin by Tim W. Brown, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0017; 1 (Box 52)
      - Janice Eidus Interviewed by Mary Mackey, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0018; 1 (Box 52)
      - WORD PERFECT 8.0 INTERVIEW NILDA CEPERO'S BLUES POEMS, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0025; 1 (Box 52)
      - MIKE DAILY RICK LUPERT INTERVIEW, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0054; 1 (Box 52)
      - Paul Agostino Interview w/Ed Stever MS Word 4.0 Virus Scanned, 1999-ycal-1021-cr-0070; 1 (Box 52)
    - Unidentified, 1996-96; 10 (Box 39)
    - Unidentified, 1996-99; 27 (Box 40)
    - Unidentified, 31 (Box 41)
    - Unidentified, 1996-99; 7 (Box 42)
  - Poetry events and music performances
    Boxes 46-50 and 51 (Record album storage) (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Poetry Festival, 1999 (Box 42)
    - "Digitas. New York Digital Review of Arts & Literature", 1 CD (Box 46)
    - Holman, Bob. "In With the Out Crowd", 1 CD (Box 46)
    - Los Bubbadinos. "Ready as We'll Ever Be", 1 CD (Box 46)
    - Ludar. "The Broughton Songs", 1 CD (Box 46)
    - Weber, Mark. "Beautemous Everlasting", 1 CD (Box 47)
    - Weber, Mark. "Bygone Tumbleweeds, Tarnation of Smoke", 1 CD (Box 47)
    - Weber, Mark. "O Shenandoah Be Not Telling Me This", 1 CD (Box 47)
    - Weber, Mark. "Words and Stories: Obligatos for Terpsichorean Dipsomaniacs", 1 CD (Box 47)
    - 3 Guys from Albany. "Performance Poetry", 1997; 1; 00:56:18; Previously recorded content can be heard in the first 56 minutes of the tape. (Box 48, Item barcode 39002099362452)
    - Elliott's Bash, undated; 1; 00:51:40 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002099362460)
    - Bogen, Laurel Ann. "The Rat City Variations", 1993, 1995; 1; 00:46:44; An echo can be heard on the tape. (Box 48, Item barcode 39002099362478)
    - "Chapter 5 & 6...of Linda reading Delilah...Lynx haiku 3/98, Sapphic Sisters Writers Workshop", undated; 1; 01:34:00; A high amount of background noise can be heard on the tape. Warble is heard during the program. Program is distorted at times. Pre-existing content can be heard at about 47 minutes. Audio is not always clear on the tape. (Box 48, Item barcode 39002099362445)
    - Church, Dave. "Bebop Rebop", undated; 1; 01:10:51; The program was recorded at a very low level. (Box 48, Item barcode 39002099362486)
      Micheline, Jack. "My City"
      Micheline, Jack. "This My Friend is How Rare Poems Are Written"
      Micheline, Jack. "Poems to Bob Kaufman"
      Winans, A. D. "Poem to jack Micheline"
      Winans, A. D. "On the Anniversary of the Death of Bob Kaufman"
      Taylor, Kent. "Brain Tumor"
      Taylor, Kent. "Calling Card"
      Taylor, Kent. "Vegas"
      Frazer, Brenda. "The Sky Can Satisfy"
      Stone, Jennifer. "The Examined Life"
      Stone, Jennifer. "Bye Bi-Sexual"
      Church, Dave. "Poor Joe"
      Church, Dave. "The Good Doctor"
      Church, Dave. "Finally Success"
      Moffeit, Tony. "You Ain't Nothin' but the Blues"
      Lerner, Linda. "Blues to Tony Moffeit on Hearing of Herbert Huncke's Death"
      Menebroker, Ann. "Three Poems"
      Savitt, Lynne. "What's Good for the Goose"
      Church, Dave. "Indian Giver"
      Church, Dave. "Sweet Mookie"
      Beck, Art. "Musician"
      Wilkinson, Wayne. "Excerpts from Crazy"
      Kaufman, Bob. "Heavy Water Blues"
      Kaufman, Bob. "I Wish"
      Nicosia, Gerald. "The Man No One Hated - To the Memory of Bob Kaufman 1925-1986
      Church, Dave. "Dade County (Cell Block B 1965)"
      Crocker, Dan. "Excerpts from: Parables for Modern Times"
      Church, Dave. "Kerouac"
      Church, Dave. "O'Henry" (1977 Short Version)
      Winans, A. D. "South of Market"
      Winans, A. D. "Dreams Long Dead"
      Winans, A. D. "The Old People of Daly City"
      McDonough, Kaye. "For Frank"
      Tsongas, George. "San Francisco"
      Tsongas, George. "The Old Man's Gone"
      Tsongas, George. "Lucky - Lucky Me"
      Tsongas, George. "Specs"
      Tsongas, George. "Poet"
      Plymell, Charles. "Buffalo Bebop Blues"
      Plymell, Charles. "Listening to Charlie Christian"
      Plymell, Charles. "Bowery Bums"
      Plymell, Charles. "Science Has Cracked the Metaphor - My Hart Crane Poem"
    - The Fabulous Dyketones. "Alive in P-Town", undated; 1; This tape was not digitized due to damage. (Box 48, Item barcode 39002099362494)
    - Jones, Seaborn. "A Poetry Reading", 1995 October; 1; 00:53:24; An echo can be heard during the program. (Box 48, Item barcode 39002099362502)
    - The Last Poets. "Time Has Come", undated; 1; 00:44:29 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002099362510)
      A list of contents are included.
      "The King is Home"
      "Kings of Pain"
      "The Time has Come"
      "Trapped"
      "Panther"
      "Down to Now"
      "For the Millions"
      "Silence of the Jams"
      "Do You Feel Good"
      "Hollow Wood"
    - "Linda's letter to Michael", 1996 December 3; 1; 01:28:13; The program is distorted at times. Sound is not always clear on the tape. (Box 48, Item barcode 39002099362528)
    - "Linda & Mary read Linda's Wu Songs + an hour of Sapphic Sisters", 1997 November 16; 1; 01:32:55; The program is distorted at times. (Box 48, Item barcode 39002099362536)
    - "Linda reads poems (1973) by Rita Mae Brown", 1997 November; 1; 00:49:08; The program is distorted at times. (Box 48, Item barcode 39002099362544)
    - "Linda reads poems of E.E. Cummings", 1999 March; 1; 01:27:03; Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 48, Item barcode 39002099362551)